I'll tell you in three.
Oh, God, that board of the Raiders gives me
Moms in Galsburg Tuesday, March 25, 2025.
Public input, that's good.
The personal period says we have nine.
Three times less.
Motion to prove.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Barnes, hi.
Jones, hi.
Parker.
Hi.
Four times less from Rans, out of group.
Motion.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Five.
Minutes from February 20, 2025, special meeting.
February 25, 2025, regular meeting.
Mark 4th, 2021.
This is back.
Good question, Mr. Steve.
I wasn't here for the 25th.
Me.
Six.
The agreement modification.
And my 166th.
Operation and agreement.
Would it be mine?
How did it go?
So this was a project that then started.
Back in 66.
They started paying pilot attacks to rescue early.
At any rate, I don't know what to forgot about it.
You can use it.
You know, how to use it?
That's over 50 something years later.
And we have to put that in dollars in this account.
That I think.
Some who are in finance to sort of stomp it all to you.
The thing about the pilot award was that the city could not use the money unless the housing authority
approved it.
So then negotiate a agreement with the housing authority, where he, we would loan or give them the $200,000 that we have.
So that they can finish the current projects that are ongoing down in finance hours and five trucks.
And they will agree to have a agreement that moving forward, they'll continue to pay the pilot tax.
And they do not have to approve whatever we do with it.
It's just restriction.
demolition or better than a housing, whether it could be.
It's 30, though.
And here?
I just like to be real off.
If we're not already motonist, we've talked about it.
Two or three are different.
We're never officially dead or not.
So we've talked about it in a couple of more accession.
But this is a,
I'll bring something.
Oh my, emotion.
No, it was the, you know what I mean?
It's like where we have the completion of the work.
And remember we talked about this.
Yeah.
We don't have any wood.
Yeah, we went toward it.
And it, well, much further delayed.
And there was that.
And but they, that didn't stop.
But that was the, they've had a completion day of December.
Right.
And January.
March.
But we also understood that why the delay is there.
Like that's why we went on the door.
And, you know, it's not, you know,
you can't just, the shower inserts for instance.
I guess I was just kind of really, you know,
my head, you know, you can't just throw a shower insert in there.
Every, every bathroom is a custom bathroom at this point.
Every, you know, fire suppression system.
Because the built-up nothings.
I, I think I can watch your imagination.
Watch your imagination.
Oh, man.
How do you, how do you, how do you do it?
So that...
Yep, day is,
I met with them two weeks ago.
Mhmm.
Um, floors.
Seven, seven, through.
Didn't something that made her shat.
Luckily, that worked out.
I would say right now,
They're about.
70.
They've actually started,
So I have to run out of time.
I can't say that they're still showing up for what they're doing, see what they're doing.
They're still working and they're still, I mean, everything's going as planned as far as I know.
Mark hasn't reached out to me as far as Steve hasn't said anything about funds or anything like that.
They're still having a way.
No, okay.
I mean.
So before we vote on this, I'm going to have to answer that.
If you guys refer for somebody to come back and answer some more questions.
For example.
Mark.
Mark McDowell is the, is the director.
It might not not fall.
Because my question is, I feel like we've powered a lot of things that are going wrong with the project
and things that should happen.
It haven't happened.
So my question is, you know, the integrity of the free construction of it.
I mean, I mean, I'm obviously going to pose.
But I think that's what's honestly, it was taken so long.
Because when they once they got into it, I realized what the integrity of the structure was.
And they're doing the best to write.
Right.
I don't want to put it in that they're, they're, it's an old building.
A lot of the concrete floors up there.
They're actually, based construction is actually taking the time to really look into this stuff and
calling it out as where some of the general, the subcontractors will just,
for a lipstick on and go, go, go on their way, but they're actually making their sub,
holding them accountable.
And they've even found entire theaters that weren't even on any of the,
and the reason, the reason we had the issue with the electric in the elevator shaft.
I asked Steve on like, how, how did this happen?
He was on vacation.
There's some, I guess, in charge when he was gone and that.
So, luckily that worked out.
Because if it went up, as far as the integrity, I feel like being involved in this whole process,
I've seen, when they'd got it, I've seen how bad it was.
And I've seen what they put back.
There was some concern with some of the cosmetic stuff.
But, yeah, I don't, I haven't, they haven't laid anything as far as getting their materials there.
I mean, like I said, they're right now, they're framing offices for the store,
front downstairs, it's getting framed, right?
That'd be, and said, that you do this.
We got to cut this corner because we don't have any,
materials and and you go on the side. So where's non-tribed that?
On tribes the north side is done. They transferred the people over to the north side and they
started getting the south side. So they hadn't started the refurbished of the south side yet, but
they're tearing down. So what's the... You want to ask their due date? I've asked multiple times
it. Like you said, it changed every time. And honestly when I asked Steve with base construction,
he can't give me a definite answer. They opened up the can of worms when they got into that,
especially in the nine of them. I have a tower just when they got in there and started getting every
time. Obviously starting with the support pillars downstairs, they were covered up and didn't know
how bad they were, you know, that delayed him quite a bit. I wonder if we thought any like before pictures,
so we could almost do like a before after a type of... I think that'd be a cool story. I mean they're finding
so many... I don't know. Sorry. I take pictures of just in my inspections when I go, but I don't know if Steve
or hopefully more than. I'm just thinking of like a little when it's done. Well we've committed this 200,000
before. Yeah. And now I don't think during a thousand's going to do anything and they can come
to us whatever we want. And it's not going to translate but we've committed to this already. Well that's right.
So that's what I said. I approve. But I just had questions and I'm like, what's going on?
So you want me to continue with the approval? Or do you want me to receive the second visit?
She's second. Oh no, but I mean... And we can... I mean if you're the more likely instead of
meeting them, we first, we can go there. I mean we can prove it and then go there.
Yeah, I don't mind how often I think that the money needs to go to. And then I think it's going to be
a year or two, go away. Right, the money does definitely need to go to them.
I naturally need to support this project. But we don't even have to have... Just go in. I go in there.
In there. We just walk in. Yes. There's just a ramp. Like they don't know who you are. It's going.
Yeah, they... They hummings. She's... She's... She's the council.
I mean if we have brought it, we'll walk through one day. She's right. There's... I mean, there's... There's no...
We just need to get the whole group one to go out. That's fine. That's fine. I would love now.
If I would be bad at the efforts, we'd get that date. But on this, we've already committed to it.
So... And we probably need Mark there with us.
Honestly, we're talking about he was going to be here tonight, but it might be my fault that he's gone.
I just texted him, but he ain't answering. I'd like to say, I haven't dealt with Mark in a while. I'd deal...
Steve, he deals with Mark, Steve's the GC, he's a superintendent on the job space.
So he's usually if I ask Mark something, he just sends me back Steve's.
This contract literally says once we give this to our thousand, the money's ours from now on, we can do it the way we want.
As long as it's our house.
I'll keep my motion now.
I'll keep my second.
Hi.
Jones, hi.
Barnes, hi.
Parker.
Hi.
Hi, Jeff.
So, we'll point a title on the Crystal Art of the 2025 represents the Grand Gateway Board of Directors for a one year time,
getting April of 2025.
So this needs to be done.
I'm here.
So I'll make a motion to approve.
All seconds.
Hi.
Jim, hi.
Barnes, hi.
Hey.
Mayor's nomination to the point Scott.
Jim, hollow to the airport board, replacing Kirk Williams.
Time to expire.
11, 7, 20.
Motion to approve.
So, hi.
Barnes, hi.
Jones.
Nine.
That's the date.
On the minor summer.
Regulation program.
MSRB.
And the boys' girls book.
Yeah.
I just want to have three of you be equipped with that day.
As a couple of you were not here when we...
What's the deal?
The deal?
The boys' girls club.
And MSRB.
The city ran in MSRB program.
And the intention...
If you go back there, we'll admit it made.
It was from my back then.
It was always kind of supposed to be the boys and girls club.
To take this over.
So once we lost in Genie Seagre.
Which we had for years.
We noticed it didn't start dropping.
And so she's the perfect opportunity to emerge the two programs together.
So this 2025, this was the first year that MSRB and the boys and girls club.
Because one, and they will take over our program.
They had open enrollment that started last Friday.
So that's why we want to get the four years that you know...
If you're getting calls regarding MSRB, please send them the name.
We'll address anything going on.
But we need to get a press release out.
We want to bring it to New Furs.
We'll make sure that the program was moving forward.
Which schools and girls club started at the point of time?
For the summer program.
I don't bless that.
For the summer program there is a fee that boys and girls club.
of those drugs. And it's always the, we have been made aware and assured that no child
will be left after all for scholarships, they offer other programs that are available.
They want them to have skin and again, and want them to be able, because it is a two-month program.
It's an all-day long program where the original MSRP was four hours on a third of a month of year.
So, but yes, there is a piece associated with the program.
That's big enough about that in the whole time.
And they get to eat their swim.
They get to eat their, they swim.
They, there's STEM programs that we could offer in the MSRP.
There's a lot of programs that we just could offer.
And the city is paying.
The city is paying $50,000 a year fee to allow, or to help us staffing for the additional MSRP students.
What do you want us to do?
What are we bringing on the new telebills and just in 2020-2024?
We brought it on in 15,000.
You know, if you ask for that 50,000 is coming from here.
Yeah.
And we use, you know, this money for, like, we just, we did the gym for a beautiful gym.
I'm going to see it.
I'm a two-month person.
You have a meeting?
Motion to approve.
I'm pretty sure.
A little bit of a bit of a choice.
A little bit of a little bit of a choice.
Well, no motion.
But if there were, I would say, where you wrote that one.
What height?
I've done it all not long.
You've been dropping a cursor on that one, too.
I was like, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do when you're standing up on this.
I was like, hey, I resent that motion.
You've been waiting for people.
You will start receiving calls.
I think once the press release comes out, people are going to wonder where they unless
I don't know if they have been that.
It's just a question for them to be in my office.
all, this is blended into the press release?
No, they were, well, I did review it and I had to do it, please do it.
Never, it's coming to you right?
So you all reviewed this, and I...
And, as a city manager, I wanted everybody to wear it.
You know, that is a granola signed year ago, so I mean, it's not very-
Everyone was a part of the granola, they were just going on.
It's 10, resolution, CC, 2025, that's your or two.
And that's your band.
23-year-long off riding V-85 support.
And V-way with Osborne Ribe's development
and the four, that 48 hours birthlet
were out looking at 15, 8 or what.
So it's same as what was in M. Shue A.
I'm going to do a pair too.
I'm a motion.
Second.
I'll see you every class.
Here's a question.
James, I farmed.
I don't want my Parker.
Hi.
I can't keep that.
Wow.
Hello.
The new business.
It may be.
Which is written with some posts in this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 pair.
Council committee announcements.
14.
So you mandatory.
So the one.
The one that happens.
We officially.
I think we reached out on Florida.
They're called in person.
So they're here.
But I just want to say thank you to Tyler.
The here you committee.
Cindy and everybody that put their dues on the right for this job.
I also received a phone call today for a friend of mine that had also an interview from
Chief.
Chief's job in his community.
He told me we actually had a home run.
And he said they.
We can't.
They hired.
The park and they didn't finish second.
He finished time for first.
And he said the guy was outstanding.
And he said the law enforcement.
No.
They got better today with our heart.
So that made me feel good about.
What you guys did.
We weren't a part of that.
The council.
Part of it.
We kind of found out when everybody else found out.
But maybe we're really good to get that phone call.
From a much larger community.
And I say much larger.
Probably one of the top 10 largest communities in Oklahoma.
He was also a.
A Bible pick for them.
And the only difference was that they're candidate.
That municipal experience.
And our candidate.
Our chief.
Had sheriff's experience.
That was the tipping for them.
Isn't that he said they were neck and neck and neck.
And both great great candidates.
And he said they're in a unique committee.
Let's split down the middle.
Half of them.
We got the hard.
They don't have one of the guy.
We hired.
So he said we got to get.
So.
You got us.
So that.
So.
Fantastic.
And we here with May 1st, I think we are going to do a meeting
probably before it comes to me, so you know, the meeting was going to be in the meeting and they could say it was coming to the council.
Can I back up?
I want to thank Dalynda and Gary, they're doing an outstanding job with a emergency management and on the street on watches and stuff, and I don't think they've been recognized enough.
But they're doing an outstanding job, and I just wanted to thank you for that.
We'll talk for you if you have 15.
Okay.